There are many ways to setup
设置编程环境的方式有很多种
a programming environment and there isn't a right or wrong way to go about it.
没有哪种方式是最正确的 哪种方式是错误的
However, if you're just starting out programming in Python,
但是 如果你刚开始学习 Python 编程
you might like to see this setup to get some ideas.
或许可以看看我要介绍的这种设置并熟悉相关界面
Over here is a text editor.
这是一个文本编辑器
This particular editor is called atom.
这个编辑器称为 Atom
But there are many additional editors I recommend in the notes below.
我在下面的注释中推荐了很多其他编辑器
A text editor is really different from a word processor,
文本编辑器与 Word 处理器截然不同
so don't mix them up.
因此不要弄混了
Code needs to be written line-by-line with intentional line breaks and
需要逐行编写代码 并故意设置一些换行符和缩进
indentations that fundamentally change how the code is read and run.
这些换行符和缩进会显著改变代码的阅读和运行方式
Good text editors have
好的文本编辑器具有一些简单但是很重要的功能
simple but vital features such as line numbers and syntax highlighting.
例如行号和语法突出显示功能
You can see the different ways atom highlights a text based on
可以看出 Atom 会以不同的方式
the types of words and objects it recognizes from the Python language.
根据从 Python 语言中识别的单词和对象类型突出显示一些文本
Syntax highlighting really helps make code more readable and organized.
语法突出显示使代码更容易读懂并且结构更清晰
It can also prevent us from making some syntax errors.
还可以防止出现语法错误
For example, if I forgot a quote at the end of the string,
例如 如果我在字符串末尾忘记加上引号
I'll know I missed it when the rest of the line is highlighted like a string.
当这行剩余部分也突出显示为字符串时 我将知道我丢失了引号
Atom knows to use syntax highlighting for
Atom 知道根据 Python 使用语法突出显示功能
Python because of this.py at the end of the file name.
是因为文件名之后的 .py 后缀
This tells atom it's dealing with a Python file.
这个后缀告诉 Atom 它正在处理的是 Python 文件
Editors are highly customizable to suit your style.
你可以根据自己的样式需求自定义编辑器的很多功能
One setting that I use is soft tabs with the top length of four.
我喜欢使用的一个设置是将 Tab 键的长度设为 4 个空格
Which means that when I press tab it is converted into four spaces.
表示当我按下 Tab 键时 它会变成 4 个空格
You can also add cool add-ons.
你还可以添加很酷的插件
Like this Python linter,
例如这个 Python linter
that uses Pylint to point out helpful things in my code.
它会使用 Pylint 指出我的代码中的实用功能
For example, in this line,
例如 在这行
pylint gives me a warning because I'm not following
pylint 显示了一条警告
PEP 8 guidelines by including a space before my closing bracket.
因为我没有遵守 PEP 8 指南 在右括号前面添加了一个空格
I also have this cool add-on which let's me use my terminal in my editor.
我还添加了这个很酷的插件 使我能够在编辑器中使用终端
Atom isn't the only thing on my screen right now.
现在我的屏幕上不止 Atom 一个窗口
I do use this terminal add-on from time to time but
我有时候会使用这个终端
generally I like to have a separate window for my terminal where I can run my scripts.
但是通常我都喜欢打开单独的终端窗口并在里面运行脚本
Generally, I can't write a whole lot of code in one go because
通常 我无法一次性写出很多代码
something will go wrong and I'll need to find the issue and debug it.
因为会出错 我需要找到问题并调试
When there's an error it will show up here when I run the script.
如果有错误 当我运行脚本时 这里将显示该错误
I make small changes to the code in
我在文本编辑器中对代码稍加修改
a text editor and then run the script again to see the output.
然后再次运行脚本 看看输出结果
If I see a problem I'll try to fix it or if things seem to be working I'll move on.
如果我看到问题 我将尝试修正该问题 如果一切正常 我将继续往下编写
I've also got the Udacity classroom and results from a question I googled in my browser.
我还打开了优达学城课堂 并在浏览器中 Google 一个问题后找到了一个答案
Normally, I'll need a browser open to look up documentation
通常 我需要打开浏览器以查找文档
or search for the solution to a bug I encounter along the way.
或针对遇到的 Bug 搜索解决方案
From now on, we recommend that you try out all your code in this way.
从现在开始 我们建议你都以这种方式尝试编写代码
Put code into a new file in your text editor and don't forget the.py extension.
在文本编辑器中将代码放入新的文件里 别忘了后缀 .py
Make sure you're in the correct directory in your terminal and then run your script.
确保在终端里进入正确的目录 然后运行脚本